=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 9=
= الحلقة 9 =
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Weiwei.
ويوي.
Dear.
عزيزي.
Mrs. Chu called me just now.
اتصلت بي السيدة تشو للتو.
She wanted to take me to a gathering
أرادت أن تأخذني إلى اجتماع
and introduce some new friends to me.
وقدم لي بعض الأصدقاء الجدد.
I feel bad to turn her down.
أشعر بالسوء لرفضها.
I see.
أرى.
Mrs. Chu's invitation is more important.
دعوة السيدة تشو أكثر أهمية.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
What's your plan today?
ما هو برنامجك اليوم؟
It's a waste if I call off the resort house reservation.
إنها مضيعة إذا ألغيت حجز منزل المنتجع.
I'll go there and relax for two days.
سأذهب إلى هناك وأسترخي لمدة يومين.
Well, then.
حسنا اذن.
Go and relax.
اذهب واسترخي.
Little girl.
فتاة صغيرة.
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Yes.
نعم.
It's for you.
إنه لك.
Don't palter with me.
لا تتحايل معي.
I haven't punished you for what you did to me yesterday.
أنا لم أعاقبك على ما فعلته بي بالأمس.
It's the cold medicine you ordered.
إنه الدواء البارد الذي طلبته.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Did you order the medicine?
هل طلبت الدواء؟
Huh?
هاه؟
No, I didn't.
لا ، لم أفعل.
I didn't order anything.
لم أطلب أي شيء.
Perhaps they got the wrong address.
ربما حصلوا على العنوان الخطأ.
Nothing's wrong with the address.
لا شيء خطأ في العنوان.
Are you Mr. Xu? The last four digits of your number are 6673, right?
هل أنت السيد شو؟  الأرقام الأربعة الأخيرة من رقمك هي 6673 ، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
I'm not.
أنالست.
Perhaps the resident downstairs wrote the wrong level.
ربما كتب المقيم في الطابق السفلي المستوى الخطأ.
I see.
أرى.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Have you done packing?
هل انتهيت من التعبئة؟
Right away.
فورا.
(Xu Xuan, did you order the cold medicine?)
(Xu Xuan ، هل طلبت الدواء البارد؟)
I filled in the wrong address.
لقد قمت بملء العنوان الخاطئ.
I'll go and take it from you.
سأذهب وأخذها منك.
If you're not in now,
إذا لم تكن موجودًا الآن ،
I'll order another medicine.
سأطلب دواء آخر.
How can you be sure
كيف يمكنك ان تكون متأكدا
that I'll come?
التي سوف آتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
A wise hunter
صياد حكيم
will show up as prey.
سوف تظهر كفريسة.
Our alliance is formed
تم تشكيل تحالفنا
at the moment you called my sister-in-law.
في هذه اللحظة اتصلت بشقيقة زوجي.
I've heard about how B.O. does in investing.
لقد سمعت عن كيفية عمل BO في الاستثمار.
But why did you put faith in me?
لكن لماذا تؤمن بي؟
Though both companies belong to Chu's family,
على الرغم من أن الشركتين تنتمي إلى عائلة تشو ،
however, Ruide aims at the potential company,
ومع ذلك ، يهدف Ruide إلى الشركة المحتملة ،
while B.O. aims at potential people.
بينما يهدف BO إلى الأشخاص المحتملين.
And this is the reason I asked to meet you.
وهذا هو سبب طلب مقابلتك.
People change.
تغير الناس.
Aren't you afraid that I change my mind?
ألا تخشى أن أغير رأيي؟
Human relationship
علاقات إنسانية
is like a pool of water.
يشبه بركة الماء.
The water level changes
يتغير مستوى الماء
when a grain of sand falls in
عندما تقع حبة رمل فيها
even though the surface
على الرغم من السطح
still seems calm.
لا يزال يبدو هادئًا.
I didn't know you were thorough
لم أكن أعلم أنك دقيق
even though you spoke harshly.
حتى لو تحدثت بقسوة.
Mutual recognition
الاعتراف المتبادل
is the prime point of collaboration.
هي النقطة الأساسية للتعاون.
You seem to have agreed to my terms.
يبدو أنك وافقت على شروط بلدي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I have to turn you down
لا بد لي من رفضك
this time.
هذا الوقت.
This time?
هذا الوقت؟
What about next time?
ماذا عن المرة القادمة؟
Not only you're thorough,
ليس فقط انت دقيق ،
but also sensitive.
لكنها حساسة أيضًا.
As the odds are different,
بما أن الاحتمالات مختلفة ،
the terms for future collaboration will be different as well.
ستكون شروط التعاون المستقبلي مختلفة أيضًا.
Ms. Xiang.
السيدة شيانغ.
I have a personal question.
لدي سؤال شخصي.
What's it?
ما هذا؟
Are you, the one from five years ago back
هل أنت من قبل خمس سنوات
or you've gotten out of the mire finally?
أم أنك خرجت من الوحل أخيرًا؟
Take a guess.
خمن.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
We're home.
نحن في المنزل.
Yes.
نعم.
What time is it?
أي ساعة؟
(Mengmeng, why don't you reply to me? Where have you gone?)
(مينجمينج ، لماذا لا ترد علي؟ أين ذهبت؟)
(I came to you as soon as I got back. Can we meet?)
(جئت إليك بمجرد عودتي. هل يمكننا أن نلتقي؟)
I can go upstairs myself.
يمكنني الصعود إلى الطابق العلوي بنفسي.
Wei will be suspicious
سوف يكون وي مريب
if you go back late.
إذا عدت متأخرًا.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Tell me when you get home.
قل لي عندما تصل إلى المنزل.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
How did you get in here?
كيف تحصل هنا؟
We've been together since we were nineteen.
لقد كنا معًا منذ أن كنا في التاسعة عشرة.
How would I forget the passcode you set?
كيف أنسى رمز المرور الذي قمت بتعيينه؟
We've ended the relationship a long time ago.
لقد أنهينا العلاقة منذ وقت طويل.
If you insist to stay here,
إذا كنت تصر على البقاء هنا ،
I'll call the police right now.
سأتصل بالشرطة الآن.
Do you think we can split with each other?
هل تعتقد أننا يمكن أن نفترق مع بعضنا البعض؟
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Have you ever wondered
هل سبق لك وتسائلت
why I came to you
لماذا جئت اليك
as soon as I got back?
حالما عدت؟
Why have we been hooking up with each other
لماذا كنا نتواصل مع بعضنا البعض
on and off all these years?
بين الحين والآخر كل هذه السنوات؟
Let me tell you this.
دعني أخبرك بهذا.
It's all written in the star.
كل شيء مكتوب في النجمة.
We're destined to be together forever.
نحن مقدرون أن نكون معًا إلى الأبد.
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
It was you who turned your back on me.
كنت أنت من أدار ظهرك لي.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Consider the thing
ضع في اعتبارك الشيء
I'm going to tell you now.
سأخبرك الآن.
Listen.
استمع.
To me,
إلي
you're the only and irreplaceable one.
أنت الوحيد الذي لا يمكن تعويضه.
I love you.
أحبك.
I love you deeply.
احبك بعمق.
I'll wait for you
سوف انتظرك
with the rest of my life.
مع بقية حياتي.
I know you're afraid of darkness.
أعلم أنك تخاف من الظلام.
Allow me to accompany you
اسمح لي بمرافقتك
when you're under the shadow, all right?
عندما تكون تحت الظل ، حسنًا؟
Where's my handphone?
أين هاتفي؟
This.
هذه.
Your shirt.
قميصك.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
You need to leave now.
أنت بحاجة إلى المغادرة الآن.
What has happened?
ماذا حدث؟
He's coming back now.
إنه يعود الآن.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
♪If you insist on leaving, I'll let you go♪
♪ إذا أصررت على المغادرة ، فسأطلق سراحك ♪
♪My love for you, I'll keep it♪
♪ حبي لك ، سأحتفظ به ♪
♪Encountering you in a different world♪
♪ مواجهتك في عالم مختلف ♪
♪I'm content♪
♪ أنا راضٍ ♪
♪With what I possessed before♪
بما كنت أملكه من قبل ♪
♪An unexpected love♪
♪ حب غير متوقع ♪
♪Is an abrupt blessing♪
هي نعمة فجائية
♪Regardless of whether your love is genuine or not♪
♪ بغض النظر عما إذا كان حبك حقيقي أم لا
♪Your place in my heart never changes♪
مكانتك في قلبي لا تتغير
♪Even if I have to be punished for falling for you♪
♪ حتى لو كان يجب أن أعاقب لوقوعك في حبك ♪
♪I'm not afraid of that♪
♪ لست خائفًا من ذلك ♪
♪Bring it on. I won't back down♪
اجلبه.  لن أتراجع ♪